(Let's say I like you.)
(Then what should I do?)
(Ryun Gi started to stir feelings in Ro Bin.)
(I thought I had made up my mind.)
(But it's changing a bit.)
(I wanted to follow my heart.)
(It would've been nice if we were together.)
(Seon Ho said some things that clearly expressed his feelings.)
(After building their connection based on a sense of certainty...)
(Honestly, all I could see was Seon Ho at that moment.)
(I wanted to go on a date with you from the start.)
(Na Young made a direct move for Seon Ho.)
(Do you want to hold my arm?)
(Can I?)
(A new sense of blossoming excitement)
(An intensifying sense of anxiety)
(Will the date sway his feelings?)
(It made my heart flutter.)
(Come on! What are you doing?)
(The start of a new relationship that may change everything)
(Love Against Time)
Shall we?
You know what? I'm feeling...
How are you feeling?
Are you pleasantly buzzed?
No. I'm just...
Why? Are you pleasantly buzzed?
Yes. Are you not enjoying this?
I'm enjoying it. Of course, I am.
(Staring)
Here's how I feel right now.
So looking at the amount of alcohol we had...
I'd feel about this buzzed after a bottle and a half of soju.
I'm serious.
- Really?
- Yes.
My body can't tolerate makgeolli.
Okay.
- That's a rice-based drink.
- Yes.
- Looking at this...
- You're right.
It's a rice-based drink.
I took a look. "What went into this drink?"
When I looked, it said it contained rice.
So I thought I might not be able to drink a lot of this.
You should stop drinking.
- No.
- Okay.
You're completely fine?
- You're not even buzzed?
- No. I'm perfectly fine.
You can tolerate a lot more alcohol than me.
- Are you feeling good?
- I feel...
- Are you buzzed?
- Yes, I'm a bit buzzed.
- My goodness.
- What?
Oh, my. Did you see that?
- "Are you buzzed?" - "Are you buzzed?"
He was flirting.
I think Seon Ho is...
quite taken with Na Young now.
- He is, right?
- Exactly.
- I agree.
- I think so too.
He was definitely flirting with her.
- He was straight up flirting.
- It would be weird...
- if he wasn't flirting.
- It'd be weird.
- He took out his secret weapon.
- Things could get out of hand.
- Are you feeling good?
- I feel...
- Are you buzzed?
- Yes, I'm a bit buzzed.
I see.
- I'm just buzzed.
- Okay.
It's not showing. So that's good.
But I look exactly the same.
- Really?
- Yes. I look the same.
But let's say I drank about three bottles of this.
Then I'd get a lot more excited than this.
(Glancing over)
Actually... I think I told you before.
So many people around me are heavy drinkers.
(Staring)
- But...
- Yes.
But if I'm being honest,
I do like handsome guys.
Let me explain. I always said,
"I don't like handsome guys."
I used to say that.
I mean, you're handsome.
And you have a beautiful smile.
So I end up smiling with you when I see you smile.
- Thank you.
- So...
So... Shall we?
(She wants to be completely honest with him tonight.)
- That's understandable.
- Isn't this cute?
What?
(An octopus-shaped sausage)
- Sorry.
- It's cute.
I... My gosh.
I'm getting tipsy.
(A night spent smiling just by looking at each other)
- Here's my complete honesty.
- Okay.
So...
I'm saying this because we're drinking together.
Okay.
We all heard the story between you and her.
Your story from six years ago.
This story could belong in a drama or something.
So I thought...
Everyone thought that you two were only interested in each other.
Hearing this kind of speculation...
made me think...
I shouldn't express my interest and complicate things.
Okay.
But then I realized something out of the blue.
- I didn't hear this from you.
- Yes.
So...
I just stopped thinking...
and decided to ask you.
That's why I chose you in the room.
After that, I thought I was quite cool for making this decision.
My gosh.
I mean, you're cool.
I'm really curious. I can't help it.
- Oh, this...
- It's not something I can do alone.
You're right. I was drawn to one person the most...
in the House.
It was fun, and I had a good time.
So I ended up going on another date with her the next day.
I liked the dates with her.
It's true that I feel attracted to her.
And...
people might think that I have my mind made up.
But I'm in the same boat. I'm not certain about my decision.
I want to spend enough time talking to other people too.
- Right.
- We don't have a lot of time.
Actually,
the only person I hadn't talked to yet...
was you, Na Young.
(The only person I hadn't talked to yet was you, Na Young.)
I really wanted to talk to you.
- Hold on.
- Wait.
- Hold on a second.
- "Na Young?" - Isn't she older than him?
She is.
- "Na Young." - "Na Young."
He just went for it.
- Yes.
- Right.
He said it so confidently.
Right. I'm curious as to why he dropped his honorifics.
Is it because she's the only one he's interested in?
Wait.
Se Young. Are you buzzed?
(Bursting into laughter)
Are you buzzed?
(They're feeling buzzed in the studio.)
- Or you're not.
- "Buzzed?"
Both of them are just unstoppable.
(Vroom)
No. Stop drinking.
He just called me by my name, "Na Young."
That made my heart flutter.
My heart raced then.
It made my heart pound. It was heart-fluttering.
Actually, that made me more interested in him.
He's more manly than he looks.
That's why it made my heart flutter.
That's why I thought Ryun Gi was pretty cool at first.
- Me too.
- And...
I thought you were cool too.
(Seon Ho said he needed time to drop his honorifics, )
(but in no time, he wasn't speaking with honorifics.)
That's how I felt.
(Heart racing)
I really liked you after we got a chance to talk.
We laughed so much and shared many stories.
To be honest, I wasn't interested in you at first.
I gradually became more interested in you.
So I wanted us to talk.
Honestly, I'd love to talk to you more.
I see.
(Seon Ho has developed an interest in Na Young.)
What about you? How was today for you?
I...
I'll answer that after this.
(Glancing over)
- Can I drink one more?
- Sure.
- The thing is, - Okay.
I might not look like it, but I do get shy too.
- But...
- So...
I really liked it.
- Really? That's good.
- Yes.
I liked it.
Today's date made my heart flutter for the first time.
(Surprised)
Gosh, this is driving me crazy. This was sudden.
But I mean it.
You made my heart flutter.
(You made my heart flutter.)
(Na Young openly expresses her feelings.)
- What?
- Well,
can I ask you what made your heart flutter?
- It's really random.
- Okay.
- I felt this way twice.
I'm sorry. It was three times.
It happened when I first saw you today.
(It happened when I first saw you today.)
I looked for you for some time, but I couldn't find you.
Then you showed up out of nowhere.
There were so many people at that crosswalk,
but all I could see was you.
My heart fluttered at that moment.
As for the second moment...
Do you remember that moment when it got super windy?
It was such a funny moment.
Yes.
It was the first time ever.
My hair had never been that messy on my first date.
But that was actually...
- It was fun for you.
- Yes.
- That moment was like...
- To be honest...
- a movie poster.
- Yes.
That's right. It was like a scene in a movie.
I thought I'd never be able to forget this moment.
Okay.
(A moment that felt like a scene in a movie)
The third moment was when we were at the N Seoul Tower.
Okay.
I was filming the view. And all of a sudden,
I wanted to record you and turned around.
(The video filmed by Na Young)
That was the third moment my heart fluttered.
(Seon Ho's smile made Na Young smile.)
What? Does it feel weird?
Hearing this is making me shy too.
Imagine how I feel to share this with you.
If anyone's shy, it's me.
It can't be if that's the case.
(Kim Na Young and Kim Seon Ho's date has ended.)
What a bummer. We're almost done with this, though.
One last shot?
(She pours their last shot.)
- We finished it.
- No way.
- Right.
Last shot?
By the way, do you want to drink more...
in the House?
Really? Okay.
(Shocked)
I really like Na Young's style.
- She's straightforward.
- Yes.
The way she said it was just crazy.
- "Do you want to drink more?" - "Do you want to drink more?"
She doesn't hide her feelings. She's so open.
That way, things can finally get moving.
I think Seon Ho likes that about her.
- Exactly. Seon Ho nodded his head.
- Yes.
Oh, no.
- Oh, my heart.
- That's Na Young's charm.
- Yes.
- Things are getting too wild now.
Alcohol is the problem.
- Seriously. It's a problem.
- It really is.
Do you want to drink more...
in the House?
Really? Okay.
(They set up a secret late-night meeting.)
How do you feel? Do you feel warm enough?
- Yes. It's getting hot now.
- Right?
It was really fun.
(Staring)
Should we go now?
(Shy)
What?
I'm sad to leave.
I want to drink more.
I was feeling good.
Oh, right.
(Their date is over despite their reluctance to end it.)
All right.
I see. No way.
I'm sad it's over.
Me too.
(They head back to the House while still longing for more.)
Do you want some?
- Do you want two?
- What? Yes.
It's small.
(Na Young gives him candy.)
- Is it watermelon-flavored?
- Yes.
- It's so good.
- Right?
Yes.
(Smiling)
- Your face looks red now.
- Yes?
Really? Oh, no.
- You can see it now.
- Yes.
- It's red?
- Yes, it's really red.
- Really?
- Yes.
Come on. This is bad.
What if they think only I drank on the date?
I'll tell them I drank more than you.
(Chuckling)
That sounds weirder.
- Really?
- Is it that red?
(Seon Ho's bold confidence puts Na Young's worries at ease.)
I'm curious, though.
- Be completely honest with me.
- Okay.
Are you interested in me or not?
Am I interested in you?
(A candid question to ask about his feelings)
- Gosh.
- What?
Come on. Tell me. Just say yes or no.
- Just that.
- I became interested in you now.
I want to talk to you more after today's date.
I want to go on another date too.
(He became more curious about her after their first date.)
I'll cut to the chase.
Do you want me to take more initiative?
Or do you want me to give you space...
and see how things go?
Given our circumstances,
I don't think we need to worry about that.
That's just my opinion.
- Really? That's good.
- It doesn't make me uncomfortable.
I just want you to follow your heart.
- I'll be honest then.
- Okay.
I'm not interested in other people.
Am I being too honest?
I just think I should be honest.
Thank you for being honest.
- If I'm being honest, - Yes.
It's true that I did spend more time with someone else.
But it's also true that I now have a lot on my mind after this date.
That actually bothered me a bit when we were drinking.
I realized that I was having a lot of fun.
Were you thinking about her?
If I didn't have fun with you on this date,
I would've made up my mind.
But...
- But that's...
- I had a lot of fun today.
You must have a lot on your mind.
What do I do?
Right. I don't know anyway either.
(Sighing)
My gosh. She just went for it.
After their date tonight,
- she'll only pursue him.
- Definitely. Only him.
I actually don't know which way Seon Ho is going to decide.
But Na Young tried everything she possibly could...
to flirt with him.
- She did everything.
- Totally.
- I want to applaud her.
- You know what?
- Seriously.
- She's so brave.
- Na Young did it.
- She did it.
- Yes.
- It was the perfect way to put it.
- She...
- Yes.
- She did it.
Seon Ho must have a lot on his mind indeed.
What are they going to do?
I guess we just have to watch how it pans out.
Seon Ho is...
Well, I'm worried about Ye Ji.
Right. I'm worried about Ye Ji.
(He has begun developing an interest in another woman.)
My gosh. One more day... We're done with Day Five.
Yes.
(The House at that time)
Why aren't they home already?
They met up late, didn't they?
Right. They did.
(When Ye Ji is getting tired of waiting, )
- What?
- Can we get out here?
- Thank you.
(the two of them arrive at the House.)
- What? Okay.
- What?
Seon Ho. Your face is red too.
- Really?
- Yes.
- It was hot. That must be why.
- Oh, no.
What do we do? Wait.
- So what?
- My gosh.
- So what? We did nothing wrong.
- So what? Yes.
- It's okay to drink.
- Drinking is fine.
What's wrong with them?
- Right.
- It's like we did something wrong.
- No way.
- What?
You said my face was red.
I wonder what everyone is up to.
I'm curious.
What?
It was crazy.
Good job.
(Everyone's eyes are on him.)
My gosh, he's back.
(Na Young quickly goes back to her room.)
- She's here!
- Oh, my. You look so pretty today.
- You look so pretty.
- What did you do?
- I drank quite a bit today.
- What?
- I drank a lot.
- Your face is so red.
- Wait.
What? Is it that red?
- Na Young.
- We wanted to drink...
Na Young dressed up to impress today.
What did you do on your date?
(Hesitant)
- Is it a secret?
- No, it's not a secret.
- What did you do?
We got on the city tour bus and went to Mount Nam.
- That's crazy.
- Oh, no. I wanted to do that too!
- Mount Nam...
- That was at the top of my list.
(Glancing back)
I'm sorry to do this.
We were on a double-decker. And the roof was done.
I'm sorry, but look. That's how my hair looked.
We kept just laughing at each other.
We were screaming and stuff.
(Feeling dizzy)
Oh, no. What is she going to do?
Oh, no.
I can't watch this.
She went on the date Ye Ji wanted the most.
- It must be agonizing to hear that.
- Right.
I might get indigestion.
Ye Ji is trying to control her emotions too.
- Yes.
- Right.
After that, we went to an izakaya and drank.
- Oh, how I envy you.
- Gosh, I'm so envious.
I want to drink too.
He wanted to drink warm sake. It was my first time having that.
Some people get drunk really fast on sake.
I easily get drunk on makgeolli.
- I can't tolerate...
- Fermented alcohol.
Rice-based drinks well.
I got drunk super fast.
- Right. Your face is so red.
- Right.
When I drink soju, my face rarely gets red.
It was so awkward, so we kept drinking shots together.
Were you able to have a meaningful conversation?
- It was very meaningful.
- That's great news.
I think alcohol definitely helped.
(Blushing)
(Sighing)
I got this hunch. Or was it just my instincts?
There was something about the vibe between them.
The two of them had drinks too.
Seeing her red face made me wonder...
what they talked about. They even drank together.
But still.
He went on three dates with me.
But this was his first date...
with Na Young.
I was worried that he might have enjoyed his date with her more.
They drank together too.
And I hear the night view from the N Seoul Tower is beautiful.
So I thought it would be impossible for a man and a woman...
to develop an interest.
I was worried.
(Pondering)
Why the long face all of a sudden?
I have a lot on my mind.
Tomorrow is our last day.
I'm most curious about your date today.
Didn't you go on a date with Na Young for the first time?
- Yes.
- It was your first date with her?
Wasn't this the first time you guys actually talked?
- It was.
- How was it?
- It was good.
- Oh, that's a positive answer.
It was so good to the point that I was glad that we talked.
I see. That's interesting.
I think this is the first time I'm hearing a positive response...
from you, so this is interesting.
Is this the first positive response?
Yes.
Do you have a lot on your mind?
No.
- Come on. He sounds so moody.
- Right.
He's gotten more introspective after today's date.
I just decided...
to follow my wild side.
- We shouldn't think here.
- Right.
- If we had fun, then we did.
If we clicked, then we clicked.
- Totally.
- Yes.
We don't have time to be thorough and check the boxes.
I don't think we should be doing that here.
Either we hit it off, or we don't.
Right.
Besides, check what boxes? This isn't a job interview.
(He decided to follow his heart instead of overanalyzing it.)
(A few moments later)
- What are you doing?
- What?
- I'm just listening to music.
I'm not doing anything.
Did you have fun?
We had drinks.
I can see that. Your face says it all.
You must be very happy.
You know...
You guys drank together.
Talking over drinks definitely changes...
- how conversations turn out.
- Okay.
It's much easier to talk.
- Right. Alcohol does that.
- It does.
Yes. It was really nice.
I bet you guys had a great time. The weather was great too.
(Thinking about her date tonight still makes her giddy.)
Have you ever been on one of those city tour buses?
- Never, right?
- No.
It was my first time today.
I always wanted to try that. But I haven't taken it yet.
Should I show you the videos I took?
- Let me see.
- It was so...
unbelievable.
- Look at that.
- Amazing.
It's crazy, isn't it?
The view is amazing.
Show him the one I was in.
- It's crazy.
- Right?
(She shows him the videos that she took with Seon Ho.)
It's a boyfriend-style pic.
No, it isn't.
Do Gon is stuck in the middle.
What's going on?
Those two should drink separately.
- The excitement is still there.
- Right.
- The joy and happiness...
- She wants to tell everyone...
- she meets.
- Right.
But she can't do that in the girls' room.
Right.
Hold on. People are gathering.
(People start gathering in the playroom.)
(She sees Seon Ho for the first time after he returned from the date.)
So, let's have a late-night snack.
I'd love that.
- Let's eat.
- Let's do that.
- Let's have a late-night snack.
- Let's have that.
Let's order in.
(The air between them feels different from earlier in the day.)
- That sounds great.
- Let's eat!
I'm excited.
- Why?
- I'm in a good mood right now.
- You look like it.
- A drunk person...
Do you need to think, Seon Ho?
- It was so disappointing.
- No.
Seeing the video, it must have been really nice.
Mount Nam was good.
- It would have been great.
- Today...
He tried to keep me calm because I was so excited.
Goodness.
(She moves away...)
(to an empty room.)
The timing always...
seems so cruel.
Also, Na Young seemed so happy.
- Right.
- That's right.
But Ye Ji, on the other hand,
seems to be having a very hard time.
How did things get like this in just one day?
Seon Ho has to tell them clearly.
He has to make himself clear.
But what if he says this again?
"I really don't know."
"I think I'll get to know at the final decision."
What if he keeps saying that?
We really have no idea either.
(Feeling confused)
(The Room of Time has opened on Day 5.)
(Do Gon came to the Room of Time first.)
(Seo Ro Bin)
Ro Bin was the only person...
I was attracted to.
I think I'll keep doing what I've been doing.
I'll express my feelings to her.
No matter the outcome.
(Do Gon allocates 100 minutes to Ro Bin.)
Do Gon.
- Seriously.
- But...
you don't find many dramas like this, right?
I don't think I've seen them.
He's like a second male lead.
- A devoted second male lead.
- When I was filming...
"You're Beautiful..."
- I used to be a second male lead.
- The second male lead.
I used to be a second male lead, and I was like that.
That kind of character.
From episode one...
- You only had your eyes...
- Consistently.
- on one person.
- to episode 16.
(Even an experienced second male lead recognizes his devotion.)
This really makes no sense.
I've never seen someone like him in real life.
(Seo Ro Bin)
(Do Gon's feelings filled another 100 minutes today.)
(Ryun Gi came to the Room of Time next.)
After talking to Ro Bin today,
(This afternoon)
(He had moments that felt like an ordinary day with Ro Bin.)
(This is nice.)
(It's relaxing.)
I feel somewhat comfortable when I'm with Ro Bin,
and our conversations just naturally flowed.
They weren't special moments,
but those moments...
always make me feel excited.
(Seo Ro Bin)
So I was certain about Ro Bin.
So I allocated 100 minutes...
not to get to know her more,
but to show...
how sure I was.
(He allocated 100 minutes with certainty.)
(Ryun Gi allocates 100 minutes to Ro Bin.)
(Ro Bin also came to the Room of Time.)
(How does Ro Bin feel tonight?)
(Kim Jong Eun)
I was so sure...
about my feelings for Jong Eun.
But I think I got confused.
(Last night)
(There's someone I want to get to know more about.)
(The night she discovered Jong Eun's guarded heart)
(Seo Ro Bin does not have a date tomorrow.)
Jong Eun's feelings weren't the same.
I think my heart gradually grew apart.
It used to be so certain.
Then,
I felt Ryun Gi slowly get closer to me.
(This afternoon)
(What should I do...)
(if I like you?)
(Do you need something else?)
(No.)
(You don't need anything else?)
(Yes. You just need to keep doing what you're doing.)
(Even when I'm talking to you, )
(I forget that I'm sick.)
(It's so nice that you said that out loud.)
(Ryun Gi's clear feelings were felt by Ro Bin as well.)
I wanted to get to know Ryun Gi...
better.
I think I wanted...
to figure out how I really felt about Ryun Gi...
by talking with him.
I wanted to check...
whether it was the comfort...
I felt as a friend...
or whether there was some romantic excitement there too.
(In order to confirm the feelings that had resurfaced...)
I allocated all the time to Ryun Gi.
(She's shocked.)
(The first 200-minute date match)
- Goodness.
- It's the first 200-minute match!
I never thought I'd see a 200-minute date match.
Exactly. I've got chills now.
- This is amazing.
- It's a 200-minute date match.
- I'm finally getting to see that.
- Ryun Gi.
It's a human triumph.
(Ryun Gi and Ro Bin are matched for a date.)
(The person Min Young's heart is drawn to)
I knew Seon Ho wouldn't choose me.
I knew Seon Ho...
wasn't interested in me this whole time.
(Kim Seon Ho)
As time went on,
I felt like I'd regret it if this was how it ended.
I wanted to make myself clear...
about my feelings.
(Min Young allocates 100 minutes to Seon Ho.)
I thought Min Young...
was interested in someone else.
(Where will Jong Eun's time go?)
(Kim Na Young)
I wanted to get to know Na Young, whom I have feelings for,
so I allocated 100 minutes to Na Young.
(Jong Eun allocates 100 minutes to Na Young.)
(Na Young came to the Room of Time.)
Of course, it's Seon Ho.
For the first time,
I made my decision without hesitation.
(The time blocks fill up quickly.)
That was my true feeling.
(Na Young allocates 100 minutes to Seon Ho.)
(What does Ye Ji think right now?)
One hundred and ten minutes.
I felt a strange vibe.
It felt like he was avoiding me.
That's why I thought,
"Something happened at that date."
"There was a change of heart."
I felt very disappointed.
I had a lot of thoughts about how to allocate my time.
(Kim Seon Ho)
I felt weighed down...
and drained.
I just wanted to run away.
(She stopped at 80 minutes again.)
(She couldn't fill the remaining 20 minutes.)
Goodness.
- She only allocated 80 minutes.
- She would feel upset.
Ye Ji shouldn't think about all that.
She should just focus...
- on her relationship with Seon Ho.
- That's right.
But Ye Ji...
also needs to say it clearly.
- Yes.
- Of course.
I think people follow the same pattern.
If I'm someone who has a hard time making decisions,
and the other person is like that too,
they'll feel like the relationship...
- will just keep going nowhere.
- That's right.
- Right.
- If one person takes the lead...
- That's right.
- and moves things forward,
- you follow that person.
- You follow that person.
- They're not exactly sure.
- Yes.
They've actually never been clear...
- about how they feel.
- Yes.
Yes.
(Kim Seon Ho, Kim Jong Eun)
(What feelings are behind the time she's chosen to leave?)
(Seon Ho came to the Room of Time.)
I'm even more confused.
I thought I'd have made up my mind by today,
but I enjoyed my date with Na Young more than I expected.
That made it more confusing.
(Two women's names are at the end of Seon Ho's gaze.)
(Kim Na Young)
(Jung Ye Ji)
It was my first date with Na Young today,
and it had a big impact.
I think I felt some romantic excitement there too.
But I've been getting to know Ye Ji this whole time,
and I really felt like we clicked.
I had feelings for her that had built up over time.
So, it somehow...
was more confusing.
(Seon Ho's hesitation is getting longer.)
So, it was...
"I don't know anymore."
(Kim Na Young)
I had a strong feeling...
that I wanted to know more about her after today's conversation.
(Kim Na Young)
(Seon Ho has made his choice.)
(What did he choose tonight?)
(Seon Ho allocates 50 minutes to Na Young...)
(and 50 minutes to Ye Ji.)
It's 50-50.
Yes.
(It's a letdown.)
As expected.
Goodness.
(The 50-minute man is back.)
Seon Ho is back.
A round of applause!
The 50-50 guy.
- Oh Tae Sik is back.
- The 50 guy.
Seon Ho is back...
- Yes.
- as the 50-50 guy.
(The Room of Time has closed for Day 5.)
- Did you decide?
- No.
- Have you figured out how you feel?
Did today's date make you think more?
Yes.
Why?
I think I'll have to see tomorrow.
- Tomorrow?
- I told Ryun Gi earlier.
I enjoyed both dates today.
But I enjoyed the one in the evening a bit more.
Would it have been different if my dates...
for the day and night were different?
Was it because what we did at the evening date was nice,
or was it because I liked the person more?
I enjoyed it more than during the day.
You enjoyed both the dates.
But it's true I enjoyed the evening one more.
I think it was a good decision to talk to her.
It was nice.
It was deep.
But I was getting to know someone else more.
So...
- I wasn't sure.
- Really?
I see.
I feel a little unsettled.
Well...
Everyone...
I feel like I'm the only weird one.
No, you're not.
Take it easy.
At your own pace.
Yes.
Don't do things...
just because the others are doing it.
Right. I'm doing my best here.
Yes.
(Kim Jong Eun does not have a date tomorrow.)
I think I'm still thinking about what I should do.
(Han Do Gon does not have a date tomorrow.)
I've been looking only at one person this whole time.
Of course, I also want...
the person I like to like me back since I'm human.
I also felt a bit bitter.
(Kim Ryun Gi has a date...)
(with Seo Ro Bin tomorrow.)
I felt really good.
I could confirm that Ro Bin...
also had positive feelings about me.
(Seo Ro Bin has a date...)
(with Kim Ryun Gi tomorrow.)
What?
- It's something else.
- Ro Bin.
The result.
I was very grateful.
On the other side, I wanted to figure out...
what the excitement toward Ryun Gi was about.
(What feelings will remain...)
(between certainty and confirmation?)
(Kang Min Young does not have a date tomorrow.)
I felt,
"How could he not allocate time to me even once?"
At the same time,
I realized how it felt.
I also don't give false hope to someone I'm not interested in.
Seon Ho is like that as well.
I could understand it so well,
so I wasn't upset.
(Jung Ye Ji has a date...)
(with Kim Seon Ho tomorrow.)
I was relieved to know...
that he allocated some time to me.
It's such a relief.
It's a bit different from what I thought.
(Kim Na Young has a date...)
(with Kim Seon Ho tomorrow.)
Whose is this?
- Isn't this yours?
- Yes.
You received a text.
So...
(Sighing)
(Ye Ji read Na Young's text by coincidence.)
- Did she see it?
- Hold on!
Did she see it?
Did she see the text?
Goodness.
(She's terrified.)
(They can't believe it.)
Why did you leave your phone there?
It's an important moment!
Why did she read it?
What are we going to do?
How could this happen?
(Seon Ho's time reached the two women.)
This is crazy.
I could feel that Ye Ji was bothered by me.
I'm going to do my best at the date.
I'll only think about Seon Ho...
at the date.
You never know how things will end up.
Honestly, who would feel good?
The person I have feelings for...
allocated his time...
to someone else and went on a date.
But now, I think the depth of it...
is different.
It could be beyond wanting to get to know the person.
He might have feelings for her now.
What if...
things really change?
(Kim Seon Ho has a date...)
(with Kim Na Young and Jung Ye Ji tomorrow.)
I felt conflicted and troubled.
What will happen tomorrow? What should I do?
Will things get certain tomorrow?
This might be exciting and nice to someone else,
but honestly, it's a hard time for me.
(A night of thoughts trailing off...)
(in the midst of unknown emotions)
(The girls' room without Ye Ji)
I need to go to bed early today.
- I don't care anymore.
- What's wrong?
My heart fluttered...
- for the first time.
- What?
My heart fluttered...
- for the first time.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Awesome.
What was it that made your heart flutter?
The thing is...
(Glancing)
My heart fluttered when we first met.
Our hearts fluttered for each other.
Seriously?
- It's like...
- Oh, my gosh!
What's more...
(Na Young's feelings grew after the date.)
And so...
It made you happy?
(Na Young can't hide her feelings.)
Seon Ho is Mr. Popular.
- Maybe it was the date.
- Sorry?
I took the bus right in front of it,
right in front of the traffic light.
Did you take the bus?
We took a city bus tour.
A city bus tour? That sounds fun.
- I'm jealous.
- It was really...
Yes.
It wasn't all that dramatic until now.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
Everything was the same. It's different every single time.
- Really?
- My dates were kind of...
I had 2 dates on the 1st day and the next day.
I had two dates.
He was someone I was most curious about.
Are you all going on a date tomorrow?
- I'm not.
- I am.
- I'll be home all alone.
What about you?
I am too.
(Glancing)
It's hard to guess who my date will be.
I wonder who everyone's dates are.
I know.
- I'm curious.
- Who's my date tomorrow?
(The late-night snack arrived.)
What's this?
- It looks good.
- Oh, my gosh.
- I'm dying to dig in.
- Same here.
(Everyone has gathered in the playroom.)
What is it?
What are you looking for?
I'm going to have leftover wine.
Wait. Are you going to drink the leftover wine?
- I'll bring it with me.
- Get me a glass.
(Staring)
(Seon Ho brought some wine to have with Na Young.)
Thank you.
It's 13.5 percent.
The drink I had earlier...
was around 15 percent.
You're tired, aren't you?
I'm a little tired, but it's okay.
I need to get some sleep tonight.
Nice.
(Seon Ho pours a glass of wine for Na Young.)
- I've been wanting to try it.
- Are we going outside tomorrow?
(The two continue to drink at the House.)
Wait. This is way better.
Right?
It's sweeter.
- This wine is less sweet for me.
- Am I...
Am I drunk right now?
- It's fine.
- No, it's not.
It smells less of alcohol.
Is that so?
It's slightly sweet.
(Ye Ji can't join in on the two's conversation.)
Right now...
Take a photo?
(Take a photo right now.)
(Seon Ho spotted Do Gon, who fell asleep.)
Make him look cool.
- He's a model for sure.
- A model is different.
Totally.
- Do Gon's nose is really...
- Pretty.
- Exactly.
- It's really pretty.
I'm jealous of his nose.
- Me too.
- He reminds me of Gong Yoo.
What?
He said you looked like Gong Yoo. Good for you.
Na Young's nose is pretty too.
- Me?
- It's sharp.
My nose is a little round.
It's kind of bent.
Oh, no. He said it right in front of her.
Hold on a minute.
To bring up...
- Na Young in public...
- Exactly.
- It's a first, right?
- What do we do?
Bringing her up in public...
- is a first, right?
- Yes.
Seon Ho just crossed the line.
With the relationship still unresolved,
I don't think it was right for him...
- Right.
- to tell Ye Ji...
where they are right now through "Na Young's nose is pretty too."
I'm sure it didn't mean too much.
He said it because her nose was actually pretty.
But saying it out of the blue...
and while everyone was there was...
This is practically a horror movie.
- A horror movie.
- Exactly.
Really.
I was quite upset about it.
The two looked close.
They kept drinking in the House.
All of that...
made me feel all dispirited.
It made me feel really...
(The two who grew closer...)
(after just one date)
(The two who grew apart...)
(after that one date)
(Before they know it, it's deep into the night.)
I'd better get some rest. I'm leaving.
Bye.
Goodnight.
(Ye Ji and Seon Ho stay behind and clean up the playroom.)
Did you have fun?
You didn't even talk to me.
- Me?
- Yes.
I didn't talk to anyone.
- What nonsense is that?
- Did I talk to anyone?
Up until a few seconds ago, you were...
I was listening.
(The conversation hardly continues.)
We're going on another date tomorrow.
- Right?
- Us.
- Yes.
You're tired, aren't you?
All day...
I've been wanting to chat with you since earlier.
I was thinking of just going to bed.
But talking before I do...
seemed like the better idea.
(Ye Ji has asked to talk first.)
- How about we talk a bit later?
- Okay.
- Or right now?
- Yes.
- Okay.
- Yes, you two need to talk.
They have to talk...
- For sure.
- before tomorrow's date.
Please talk, you two.
Ye Ji, there's no time to go back now.
It's awkward, and very much so.
(Sighing)
(The 2 get to talk for the 1st time tonight.)
(Seon Ho drops by his room for a second.)
(He takes a jacket for Ye Ji.)
(Handing over)
No problem.
This jacket is thick.
Yes, it's thick.
(Ye Ji wears Seon Ho's jacket.)
(Glancing)
The night air feels nice.
Right? Even the sky was clear today.
I just wanted to ask how...
today went.
Today?
It was...
(Even the simple question is tough to answer.)
Honestly, here's what crossed my mind.
I had one person I wanted to talk to more.
- Was she your date today?
- Yes.
So I thought I'd find out today.
If we weren't on the same page and our conversation was mediocre,
there'd be...
one less person I'd be interested in.
But it...
When I had the lunch...
- Yes?
- and dinner dates,
the date I had at dinner was a bit more...
I liked the dinner date more.
But...
What confused me the most was...
whether I had more fun because...
the date course was much more enjoyable...
or because my date was more interesting.
I couldn't really tell.
(Seon Ho honestly expressed his current feelings.)
My heart sank big time.
I had some trust in him.
I thought, "No way his feelings would waver."
But his feelings did waver.
Whether it was because of his date or the atmosphere.
Honestly, it was a shocker.
So...
what I was worried about actually happened.
Despite all that,
we had spent time together until now.
Give me a moment.
No. Don't cry.
(Upset)
This is really upsetting.
It was just yesterday.
It was just yesterday that...
Seon Ho got jealous.
Seon Ho expressed that he had gotten jealous.
After hearing that,
Ye Ji realized that he was the jealous type...
and that he was interested in her.
Because of that, Ye Ji enjoyed the date more...
- the next day.
- Correct.
- That was during the daytime today.
- Yes.
With all of that going on, he suddenly said on that very night,
"The date I had with the girl I was curious about was..."
"more fun."
In short, in Ye Ji's shoes,
- it's a very upsetting situation.
- It surely is.
It's a heartbreaking situation.
Ye Ji must feel confused.
Talking to you was great.
But spending time with a different person...
I don't know what that means to me.
It's hard to judge with just one day.
Even I could tell that.
Tell what?
The evening date must've been memorable.
- I see.
- Yes.
Maybe, even more memorable than the daytime date.
- The daytime date was nice too.
- It's just that...
I could tell.
For now...
(The silence between the two grows longer.)
- Did things get complicated?
- What?
Did things get complicated?
(Thinking)
(Ye Ji can't answer right away.)
Today was, in many ways...
I'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
It's just...
I feel like the cause.
I really don't want you to mind me.
But it's not as if I don't mind you at all.
Seon Ho's feelings.
And my feelings. It's best to be faithful to them, no?
On the last day.
True.
Thank you for being honest with me.
Either way, you and I have a date tomorrow.
(Ye Ji tries hard to talk as if nothing's wrong.)
During the date...
Let's talk.
Wouldn't that be okay?
(Sighing)
Do you have anything more to say?
Shall we go inside?
(Faced with how different Seon Ho seemed, )
(Ye Ji hid her feelings.)
(Upset)
What now?
At least Seon Ho told Ye Ji his feelings before tomorrow's date.
- Even Ye Ji needed that chat.
- Yes.
It was much needed, but it's heartbreaking.
Had tomorrow come...
with things still up in the air...
- That'd be worse.
She wouldn't know how to act.
This is tough.
(Before they know it, the sixth morning has arrived.)
What do I do?
I have no idea what to do during today's date.
What's best is to be yourself.
But you know...
It keeps bothering me.
The fact that his feelings are growing for someone else.
You shouldn't wish Seon Ho to give you a definite answer.
Right? He kept being wishy-washy.
- When I had...
- Exactly.
Just made up my mind yesterday,
- he suddenly acted all different.
- You never know.
It's driving me crazy.
Is it best to give him assurance?
What if he feels some pressure...
- You should.
- from it?
But stepping back now, after all this time, is a bit...
- Is that so?
- What you should do is...
What do I wear for the date?
(Glancing)
Should I wear this? It's pretty.
(Ye Ji leaves the room.)
I have a feeling...
Seon Ho is going through a really tough time mentally.
Of course. I'm sure...
- he's not that type of person.
- Talking to both of us...
Having to think about several people must be tough.
(Meanwhile, Seon Ho is ready for the date.)
(He heads to the girls' room.)
(Knocking)
(Signaling)
What?
(Seon Ho calls over Ye Ji first.)
(Ye Ji looks brighter.)
I wasn't going to let it bother me,
but it does bother me.
(Seon Ho is off on the date with Ye Ji.)
"Come home quickly," was what I thought.
(She watches the video from last night.)
Wait.
Na Young?
- Seriously.
- Wait.
How many times are you watching it?
Goodness.
She's watched that video...
four thousand and two hundred times.
(Laughing)
The viewers wouldn't know because of all the editing.
- She saw it 4,200 times?
- Yes, 4,200 times.
Gosh, it must be worn out by now.
She's going to watch it over and over again until the date.
(Seon Ho is all Na Young can think about.)
(Sighing)
(Yongsan-gu)
What great weather.
- Where is it? Is it on the left?
- Over there.
(Ye Ji and Seon Ho's last date has begun.)
- Let's go inside.
- Okay.
- Welcome.
- Hi.
Hi.
- Party for two, yes?
- Yes.
Choose a table, and I'll bring over the menu.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
(Their last chance to spend time together)
- Enjoy.
- Thank you.
(Awkward)
- Today's weather is so amazing...
- Yes?
That...
it feels like we're out to heal.
Totally.
How should I approach this date? What mindset should I have?
Should I act as if I'm fine?
Or should I share...
my heartbroken feelings?
After thinking things through,
as this was our last date,
I tried to act bright...
as if everything was fine.
Do you like pudding?
I do.
It's good,
- especially caramel pudding. Yes.
- Caramel pudding.
(An awkward silence follows their brief conversation.)
Yesterday, I was very worried...
A lot went through my mind.
(Sighing)
Yesterday...
Yes?
Shall we drink first?
Well, cheers.
How did you feel after our talk yesterday?
First of all,
- I was glad that we talked.
- Right.
If not, I would've come to the date...
without knowing anything.
Well, I'm sure it wouldn't have been much different.
But still,
I was thankful that you told me about how you felt.
And...
- it was totally understandable.
- Right.
Based on your character, I'm sure you felt...
bad about it.
It must have been hard even to bring it up.
- Right.
- I thank you for telling me.
But I'm fine with it.
It's up to you what you do.
- Right.
- I will do what I choose to do.
I hope that you won't feel bad about it.
We should just...
- Tomorrow is the last day.
- Right.
We should just do the best we can until that time...
- at our own places.
- Right.
You were able to meet...
- the others.
- Right.
You were able to spend time with them,
and I feel good about that.
Right.
I would've felt uncomfortable about it...
if you didn't meet the others.
Thank you for saying that.
(Letting out a sigh)
Do you think you spent the week without any regret?
Yes. Well, I thought,
"Would anything actually happen?"
I was worried before I got here.
Right.
But changes happened all of a sudden.
There were times...
when I suffered emotionally.
There were good days as well. I went through mood swings...
within just one week.
It was as if I was on a roller coaster.
My feelings went up and down.
That made me feel surprised about myself.
Actually,
if I look back through my life,
I wasn't able to approach someone first to express my feelings.
I was someone who always kept my feelings hidden.
- Right.
- But...
we're in an extreme situation.
No matter how timid I was,
I had to be active and ask for a conversation.
I had to express myself.
My actions felt so unfamiliar.
I wasn't sure if it was right to start a conversation.
No. I felt thankful that you started a conversation with me.
- After talking with you, - Yes.
I was glad that we talked.
I wanted to tell you anyway.
If we didn't have a conversation yesterday,
- I was going to tell you today.
- Right.
I knew how you were going to feel.
It would've been tough to bring it up today.
You started a conversation with me yesterday,
and that became an opportunity to talk about that.
It would've been something upsetting to hear,
but you listened to what I had to say.
It felt like...
- you understood me.
- Right.
Well,
I'm in the same position.
Anyone could feel curious.
We have limited time to spend with each other as well.
We should carry on...
with the heart we'll feel at the final moment of tomorrow.
Let's do our best until tomorrow.
What?
- They're not breaking up, are they?
- Why does it feel sad?
Why do they sound like people breaking up?
- Right.
It doesn't feel like a date. They're both thinking,
"Must it be that way?"
"Must I do that for him or her?"
It feels like a duty.
- Right.
- Why?
- It ended up like this...
- after last night.
- Right.
- It's not a date.
- They feel bad for each other.
They feel bad for each other.
They keep feeling that way.
But there's no need for them to feel that way.
(Feeling upset)
(Sighing)
(Kim Seon Ho and Jung Ye Ji's date has come to an end.)
It ended really quickly today.
(The two of them received the final text message.)
Do you feel sad about it?
I do.
I want to stay here longer.
- I wish we had more time.
- Right.
You're such a busy guy.
- So busy.
- Right.
Gosh.
Anyway, have a good time today.
- Right. I'll see you later.
- Right.
I'll see you at the House.
- Rest up well.
- Okay.
(Time went by faster than ever.)
There's a car coming. Let's move slowly.
(Their last date has come to an end.)
(The House at that time)
- I thought you were in college.
- Really?
- You look so young.
Really?
(Ryun Gi and Ro Bin head out for their date.)
- The weather is so nice.
- Hey, take my hand.
(Holding)
Done.
It feels like Animal Crossing with these two.
- Right!
- Right.
It's a therapeutic moment.
"Hey, take my hand."
She's such a teto-girl.
Ryun Gi's heart...
- is set toward her.
- He feels so happy.
- Right.
Ro Bin would've felt that.
- Will she see him as a friend...
or will she start to develop feelings for him?
Ryun Gi should keep knocking at the door of her heart...
- without giving up.
- Right.
- He should keep it up.
I hope she slowly plunges into his charms.
- Slowly.
- Right.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- The weather is great.
- The weather is so nice.
- It'll be perfect without the wind.
- Right.
- You're the weather fairy.
- The wind...
The wind feels warm. It feels nice today.
Right. It feels warmer than yesterday.
Right.
The weather is...
much better.
(Yongsan-gu)
(A cute restaurant that suits the two)
Karashi.
- Karashi.
- Japanese vibes.
I love it.
Hello.
- Hello.
Sit to the left.
- Here?
- Yes.
The weather is so nice.
Thank you.
What should we have?
Awesome.
(Focused)
- This.
- Right.
- Should we do that?
- Right. Let's do that.
Okay. Do you want any drinks?
They must not have regular soft drinks.
- They don't?
- They're all alcoholic drinks.
There are non-alcoholic drinks as well.
Where?
There's the non-alcoholic highball.
- Coke and Coke Zero.
- Gosh.
Should we get a Coke Zero?
- Should we get a Coke Zero?
- Sure.
We'll get these two...
- and a Coke Zero, please.
- Right.
Thank you.
- The weather is so nice.
- Right.
- How do you feel?
- About what?
- It's the last day tomorrow.
- Right.
It's going to be hectic tomorrow.
- We won't be able to spend time.
- Right.
Today is an important day, isn't it?
What do you think?
- Me?
- Yes.
Did time go by quickly?
It did.
Time went by quickly, and it felt too short.
- Right.
That is why I have a lot going through my head.
- What about you?
- You have a lot to think about?
Me?
Well,
I do have a lot to think about.
when I went...
to do the laundry yesterday,
things became clear for me.
- Really?
- I felt that I didn't have to...
- think anymore.
- Right.
(I felt that I didn't have to think anymore.)
That is why I don't have that much to think about.
(Surprised)
(He shares his certainty toward Ro Bin.)
Thank you so much for being honest about it.
- You should think about it.
- Right.
It's right for you to think about it.
But today, I want to have fun with you...
without thinking about anything else.
- That can't happen.
- Why not?
- You can't go completely blank.
- No.
- Well, the complicated thoughts.
- Good.
- I was joking. That sounds good.
- Right.
- Let's try later.
- Oh, right.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
It's been a really long time since I've had Coke Zero.
- You don't drink carbonated drinks?
- I don't.
What? I also don't drink carbonated drinks.
Really?
You ordered this because of me, right?
Yes. What about you?
I ordered it because of you.
Should we get whatever we want to drink?
Let's do that.
(They ordered the drink for each other.)
You two are really close.
- Gosh!
- Right.
You two are touching! You two are about to touch!
Ryun Gi looks comfortable.
Right. A lot more comfortable. How cute!
When you see considerate couples,
there are times when...
they order things for each other while assuming that...
- Right.
- they would like them.
They would both eat things that they don't like.
Isn't this something you can't have?
To be honest, I can't drink it. I can't have carbonated drinks.
- I'll drink it.
- Just pour it for me.
Okay.
- Hey!
- What is it?
Shall we clink our glasses?
(Taking a bite)
Actually,
- I wanted to ask you this.
- What is it?
I wasn't able to bring it up...
- as it was something personal.
- Right.
If I remember it correctly,
you said your father was watching over you from above.
May I ask when he left?
It was when I was in ninth grade.
My dad...
didn't suffer from an illness.
He just passed away all of a sudden.
There was no specific cause? It was just an acute disease?
Right.
Back then,
I was young, but I was old enough to know what was going on.
It happened so suddenly,
so...
I started to fall into darkness...
since then.
After my dad passed away,
I didn't know how to express my feelings.
All of my family members felt very sad.
I've never heard those sounds of wailing before.
The sounds of their wailing were a great shock to me.
As they were a great shock to me,
I didn't want to make those shocking sounds with them.
That was why I didn't cry.
But...
my family wanted to know...
why I didn't cry.
I think I tried to avoid that situation.
Well,
I'm not sure.
I don't know how to describe that emotion.
Even I struggle to understand what it was.
After I got sick,
there was a time when I cried my eyes out.
But at that moment,
the things stuck inside my heart were released.
I started to cry a lot more after that moment.
But I still struggle to cry in front of others.
That must be why...
your mother loved you twice as more.
My mom? Right.
My sisters did a lot for me as well.
- Right.
I prepared these this morning.
These postcards...
- were picked with great care.
- Right.
I bought these based on the images...
- of the people in the House.
- Right.
They each hold a special meaning.
- I got this one.
- That's amazing of you.
Will you give these out today?
Yes. After writing in each one.
- Really?
- Yes.
Are you serious?
- Who do you think this is?
- Right.
Who could it be?
This is you.
- Why?
- What?
I told you this. Your first impression...
- felt pure and clear.
- Gosh!
Gosh!
I didn't finish writing them,
but I wrote yours first in the morning.
(Surprised)
I was going to give it to you last, but we had our date today.
When should I read it?
- You can read it now.
- Really?
You can read it now.
I was going to give it to you last,
but I prepared it before coming out this morning.
- I wrote it in advance.
- Gosh!
(Ryun Gi wrote a letter for Ro Bin.)
Your handwriting is so nice.
What? I scribbled the words.
(To Ro Bin)
(Hi, Ro Bin.)
(You are someone who gives off the beautiful love of your family.)
(You are a comfortable person who makes me forget my pain, )
(and it always makes me feel amazed and grateful.)
(I hope our relationship lasts for a long time.)
This is awesome, Ryun Gi.
This is awesome.
The very first gift.
Thank you so much. I didn't prepare anything for you.
You didn't have to.
Really? Gosh.
(Ryun Gi shared his heart through the letter.)
Thank you, Ryun Gi.
My heart fluttered the most when I got his letter.
He calmly explained...
why he chose the postcard.
He felt attractive as a man,
and it made me want to know more about him.
Most importantly,
he made my heart flutter.
- Gosh, what?
- Gosh!
He did well to get the letter.
- Right.
- Right. Ryun Gi.
He only said she was the first one to get it.
- He's so considerate.
- Ryun Gi...
- thought about the date all day.
- Right.
- You can feel it!
- From start to finish.
- He feels more comfortable now.
- You can feel it.
- Right.
"What kind of date should I go on with Ro Bin?"
You can feel that he thought about this all day.
This was what we wanted.
Right.
They're certainly more than friends now.
- More than friends.
- Right.
- They're not just friends.
- They get 100 points.
- They get 200 points.
- There can't be...
a better date than this.
Nice.
Gosh.
Gosh, Ryun Gi. You are seriously...
You're someone who can't be described with words.
- I got a text.
- This is so touching.
- Really?
- Yes.
- What a relief.
- I felt so touched.
(Kim Ryun Gi and Seo Ro Bin's date has come to an end.)
- Gosh.
- What's wrong?
- It's over.
- It's over?
It's over already.
(Disappointed)
Right.
Shall we get going, then?
- Give me a second.
- What's wrong?
- What?
- I need to digest the food.
- Oh, right.
- Should I pat your back?
- Sure.
- Is it here?
- Yes, there.
- Here?
- Yes.
- Is this the spot?
You know how babies need to be burped, right?
Right. I've done this a lot for my nephew.
- Right.
- It's done like this.
Right. "Burp."
Isn't she such a cute person?
The times I spent with her felt so tingly.
My heart pounded like crazy.
I think a slight rub will work.
(Smiling)
Gosh, that's good.
Didn't I struggle to speak today?
Didn't I sound different today?
- You stuttered?
- Right?
- Did you stutter?
- Didn't I stutter today?
- I didn't notice it.
- You didn't?
(The last date started a pleasant excitement.)
- Gosh, it's been so long.
- Yes!
The therapeutic couple.
That was such a comfortable date.
- This is a true date.
- Right.
- This is a true date!
- Exactly!
Gosh, it was a pleasant moment.
It felt like a peaceful movie.
- It's so relieving.
- It's so relieving!
They weren't the 200-minute couple for no reason.
- Right.
- The storyline was perfect.
- It was perfect.
Starting from the first episode.
- It's so relieving!
- Gosh!
- That feels great!
My medicine was here.
- You're right about that.
- My medicine was here.
- The medicine was right here.
- Gosh, I love it.
(Greatly satisfied)
(Singing can be heard out of nowhere.)
You should sing with me.
(Do Gon and Jong Eun are enjoying an outdoor karaoke date.)
(Bursting into laughter)
They must've had a blast.
Won't these two head out while holding each other's hands?
The best couple is right here.
Right.
(Don't hide it)
(You're not alone)
(Meanwhile, Ye Ji returns to the House alone.)
(Jong Eun's second performance without Ye Ji)
I pretended to be cool about it on the outside.
"Get to know about others." I pretended to be cool about it,
but I was rotting inside.
It even made me tear up.
Who would want a person they're interested in...
to go out on dates with someone else?
"What must I do about this situation?"
(While Ye Ji's thoughts become more complicated...)
Did you have something?
I didn't eat anything.
- Really?
- I'm so hungry.
Oh, right. I did have coffee and pudding.
- But...
- I really want coffee right now.
I want to have more coffee too.
- Are you hungry?
- A little.
Do you enjoy having brunches?
I didn't have them often.
(The two head over for brunch.)
- It feels quite awkward, right?
- Yes.
It's too...
A lot of things happened yesterday.
I'm curious about how things are going right now.
Do you feel awkward?
Do you feel awkward about me or this situation?
Both.
- Really?
- Yes.
But you looked so comfortable when having a drink with me.
(Embarrassed)
- So?
- Yes?
Why do you feel awkward?
- Stop. I can't handle these things.
- What?
I feel awkward...
about these things.
I know.
That was why I tried to joke about it more.
(Thinking)
Was it okay for you? We drank yesterday.
It felt like you opened up more after getting a drink.
- Well, that's that.
- Right.
Having a drink...
gave me a bit of help.
I didn't exactly say that because I had a drink.
I wondered if you regretted saying that.
Not at all.
Okay.
I feel shy about it.
Actually,
- after going on a date with you, - Right.
I thought that I would be able to make up my mind...
after learning about you.
But that confused me even more.
This is what I think.
To be honest, I enjoyed the date we went on at night...
out of the two dates I went on.
(I enjoyed the date we went on at night.)
So...
I believe...
things might become clearer after talking to you today.
After going on...
another date with you.
Well, as for me,
I thought that you would feel more comfortable...
if I opened up more.
- It wasn't to pressure you.
- Right.
To be honest, you're the first one...
I felt attracted to...
after coming here.
- Really?
- Yes.
I'm being really honest.
So...
Gosh, this is crazy. So...
What about you?
During the date with you,
I did feel attracted to you.
I didn't expect you to feel shy, but you did feel shy.
Isn't it quite bad?
- I get really shy.
- Right.
I saw a completely different side from what I expected.
"So she's like this as well."
The more I talked with you,
the more I enjoyed it.
You made honest and bold comments,
but you felt shy after saying those things.
And...
I wanted to...
tease you even more when that happened.
I stopped saying things out of shyness.
I noticed myself going through those changes,
and I realized that my heart was fluttering.
(Feeling shy)
"I must be thinking about him."
This was what I thought.
(Gulping and letting out a breath)
Gosh, I'm sorry.
The gulp was so loud.
Gosh, she's so straightforward.
This is Na Young.
"I'm going to settle things today."
- This is her mindset.
- She has nothing to lose.
She might even make him...
- choose her.
- That's right.
But Ye Ji can't say that.
- Ye Ji can't say that.
- No.
Na Young has the advantage in this situation.
- Right.
- It's making us watch...
- while holding our breath.
- Right.
- It's like we're spying on them.
So...
I thought a lot about...
how to express myself...
without making you feel pressure.
No. I like you being straightforward.
I'm doing that as well.
My heart fluttered yesterday as well.
I felt very attracted.
It impacted me a lot.
Also, the outfit you wore...
surprised me as it was different from your usual outfits.
When I first saw you, I went,
"What?"
- I smiled.
- Right.
Was that why you smiled?
It was part of it.
You must've been surprised.
I felt happy, shy, and awkward.
There was a mix of emotions...
during that moment.
My heart fluttered the whole time.
What is this? This is a situationship.
It was so exciting. It felt like an actual date.
I was certain about wanting to know more about him.
I was curious about him, and I kept thinking about him.
In any case,
I was attracted to him.
I had that feeling toward him.
I developed a stronger desire of wanting to know more about him.
(Na Young honestly expressed her feelings.)
(At that time)
(Ye Ji is lost in her thoughts.)
(Her tears suddenly burst out.)
The time of waiting...
was quite tough to handle.
I got mad and felt anxious.
I experienced a storm at that moment.
It was...
tough to handle.
It felt like I was breaking down.
Well,
it made me think,
"I think I won't be able to handle this."
"This might be the end."
I couldn't do anything about feeling upset about it.
"This must be the end for us."
(Love Against Time)
(D-1 before final decision)
(It felt like I was going to regret it.)
(Who are you concerned about the most at this moment?)
(Say it right away. Is it me or her?)
(The truth can no longer be kept away.)
(The game was no longer needed.)
(I felt certain about it.)
(This is driving me crazy.)
(A shocking text message gets sent to everyone.)
(Am I getting it all wrong?)
(I wasn't able to handle it.)
(The text message brings change.)
(It was only you, Ro Bin.)
(I did feel shaken.)
(Will a new future unfold?)
(Shall we talk?)
(Things happen so quickly.)
(It's different each day.)
(I want more time to think.)
(This is driving me crazy.)
(4 names)
(Only one piece)
(In between certainty and anxiety, )
(it's hard to predict what will happen.)
(What will be the result of the final decision?)
(Love Against Time)